(Raj:)It's funny because bread sounds like dead.
(Penny:)I'm sorry,
but these are just ordinary foods...
(Sheldon:)...with the names bent into tortured puns.
But the dishes themselves
are in no way Halloweeny.
(Raj:)Ooh, Hallow-weenies.
(Raj:)That's a good one. They'll pair nicely
with my Draculoni and Cheese.
(Raj:)How do I do it?
Reminds me. I was thinking of wearing
my NASAjumpsuit as a costume...
...but I realized everybody would be like:
"Where's your costume?
Why are you wearing work clothes?"
(Leonard:)Hello, boys.
(Sheldon:)What are you smiling at?
(Leonard:)Nothing.
- You know where there's a lot of nothing?
- Space.
(Howard:)Boy, it's nice to sleep in a bed
with gravity again.